Madame is right. Maybe l am special.l can be anything l want.
夫人说的没错  也许我是特别的  我能成为我想的一切
With colors so bright
色彩如此明艳
It always reminds me of Spring
它让我想起春天
And ringing my bell just makes me want to sing
铃儿响让我想歌唱
The air is so rosy, so sparkly and light
氛围如此瑰红  如此灿烂轻快
lt's golden all day and deep purple at night
白天是金色  夜晚是深紫
Riding along makes me feel so happy
骑车让我感觉如此开怀
The city is shining, its colors are snappy
城市在闪耀  色彩欢蹦乱跳
The sky is so blue and the buildings all gleam
天空如此蓝  建筑在闪
lf l wasn't awake, l'd be in a dream
如果我没有醒  我是在梦乡
Ring a little bell and off l go singing
按动小铃儿  我放声歌唱
The colors keep time to my bell's ding-a-linging
色彩合着我的铃儿叮叮响
A bright little tune l will sing from the start
欢快的小曲我将从头唱
The song that l sing also rings in my heart
我唱的歌也在我心里响叮当